Excuse me, ladies. Excuse me.
How did you guys get rich?
You can ask her that question.
Yeah? How did you get rich? How
old were you when you became a millionaire?
I was 22 years old.
You said 22?
How do you know?
I'm 34.
How did you get rich? What did you do?
God made me a millionaire.
How did you really do it? Who is your God?
Jesus Christ, my Lord and Savior.
And what's your name?
My name is Jameis Winston.
And what do you do?
And I'm an NFL quarterback
for the New York Football Giants.
I was in the logistics business. I ran
a big look at the trucking company, sold it.
I started from nothing. Two trucks, empty
warehouse, built a lot of real estate.
How much did you sell your company for?
$400 million.
Sold a company for $400 million?
Over $500.
$500 million.
How did he get rich?
No.
You got to ask him. He
got the best story in America.
How did you get rich?
You won't believe it.
How did you get rich,
man? How did you get rich?
If me and you died tomorrow, and you had one more
message to leave with the younger generation, what would that be?
The biggest advice I can give anybody is first...
This is New York City.
The richest city in the world.
And I'm not kidding.
More billionaires, more millionaires, more money moves in this
city every day than anywhere else on the planet.
So today, I'm doing something insane for you.
I'm going to be investigating New York
City by going straight to the source.
I'm going to be interviewing the millionaires and the billionaires of
New York City to figure out how they built their wealth.
These are the people who've made it
in the most competitive city on Earth.
Because like they say, if you can
make it here, you can make it anywhere.
So this is my investigation into
the richest city in the world.
Let's get this video on the way.
The Richest City in the World
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, I had a question for you.
What, sir?
Real quick, sir.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Alright.
Excuse me, sir.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Never mind.
I don't know.
Real quick, sir.
Could I get one minute?
I'm sorry. No.
Like and subscribe to the channel.
Oh my God.
Let's go.
Wait, wait.
Excuse me, sir.
I have a question for you.
Look, I'm a phone call.
Real quick, sir.
So I grew a channel to
20 million followers in Austin, Texas.
I go all over the world asking people.
Hang on, hang on.
I got to go.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Alright, man.
Damn, bro.
Excuse me, sir.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I'm not a millionaire.
What line of business are you in, sir?
I'm an independent consultant.
Yeah?
I'm an angel investor.
Why do most businesses fail in today's world?
Eight out of ten companies
don't make it past five years.
I don't know.
I need to think about that one.
Yeah.
So real quick, sir.
I grew a channel to 20 million followers.
Any of you are the most successful
business owners like Mark Cuban, Michael Rubin, Shaq.
Could I get just 30 seconds?
It'll be worth it.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Alright, man.
Have a good one.
Man, look.
As you guys can see, man.
Look, we've been trying all day out here to
try and get these people to stop and do interviews,
man.
That's an angel investor.
Sounds like he might be from the UK, man.
But look, I'm not going to stop, man.
Look, we're the richest city in America, man.
There's more millionaires and billionaires in
New York than anywhere else on earth.
So let's go find out where
they are and how they got rich.
Come on.
Excuse me, ladies.
Excuse me.
How did you guys get rich?
I'm going to ask her that question.
Yeah?
How did you get rich?
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I was 22 years old.
You said 22?
How do you know?
I'm 34.
How did you get rich?
What did you do?
I was the founder of an app called Sweat.
And then we sold.
How much did you sell your company for?
400 million.
You sold a company for 400 million?
Could I interview you for a minute real quick?
I go all over the world interviewing
the richest people to help the younger generation.
I follow you.
I've seen all your stuff.
Is that cool?
Yes, of course.
Of course.
Okay.
Where are you from?
I'm from Australia.
What's the biggest difference doing business
in Australia versus the United States?
Oh, this has got a big hustle culture.
Like, everyone's moving.
Australia is way more chilled.
But it's amazing.
Did you come from a lot of money?
Absolutely not.
No, not at all.
No, I actually started my Paris backyard.
Did you have any investors in the company?
Did you bootstrap it?
Bootstrap the whole thing.
The entire thing?
Yes.
To 400 million?
Yeah.
I'm going to challenge you right now.
Take me back to the
most life-changing conversation you ever had.
What is the greatest piece of advice
that you ever received throughout your career?
The greatest piece of advice
I've ever received is someone said,
you know that you are under no obligation
to be the same person you were yesterday.
And I think that is really
strong in the fact that, like,
it might be your fitness journey that you're on.
You're under no obligation to be
the same person you were yesterday.
You can change.
You can make a change.
But same with business.
Like, people know you for such a niche.
And a lot of people listening to this,
they will know that person for that niche.
They'll know you for this niche.
But you don't have to be
the same person that you were yesterday.
You can go off.
You can change.
You can do something different.
And I think that this year for me is
a big focus on growing myself and my brand
and doing other things other
than just being a personal trainer.
So as a woman in business,
did you have people that doubted you?
Absolutely.
And still to this day.
But even, like, for example, I grew up Greek.
So, like, my grandparents have no idea.
They still don't know what I do.
My family was like, personal
training is not a sustainable career.
At some point, like, I do agree with them.
And a little bit of me
was like, should I be doing this?
But then when I pursued the career and
then when I cut out half the market,
when I did the guys, when I
did the app, and then when I sold,
like, you kind of get to prove
them wrong, but in a nice way.
And they really, really appreciate what I do now.
What's the number one thing that business owners get wrong
when they try to sell their company?
I mean, I think I did it wrong.
I think, like, when you're selling a company,
you want to be able to sell the
company that doesn't have you attached to it.
And I think what I
did wrong and where I would,
if I could do anything
and do it all over again,
is I would remove myself as part of the company.
You want to sell it and
be able to celebrate and relax.
But for me, it wasn't relaxing.
They call that the key man risk.
That's right.
That's why they say that Disney's the best business
because Mickey Mouse isn't in the negotiations.
That's exactly right.
I love that.
So there's some truth to that right there.
Absolutely, there is.
You made a lot of millions in your career.
How does somebody make their money work for them?
Don't put all your eggs in one basket.
So make sure that you diversify your wealth.
For me, the first thing that ever made me money
that I was so excited that I bought
was a petrol station.
Gas station?
A petrol station, gas station.
You bought a gas station?
Yeah, and I was like, wow,
out of all the millions of dollars,
it's so cool to see rent
coming in from a gas station.
It was like doing different things,
investing in property, investing in the market,
like just diversifying your wealth
and not putting it all in one basket.
Because one day the internet might shut off
and it'll all be gone.
You never know.
That's right.
What's your name?
My name's Kayla Otinas.
And if me and you died tomorrow
and you had one more message to leave
with the younger generation, what would that be?
I think what I said before,
you're under no obligation
to be the same person you were yesterday.
You can make a change.
If you have a passion, go for it.
You got amazing advice.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate that.
I connect with all the millionaires
and billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Of course.
Okay.
$400 million is what she
sold her company for, you guys.
And she just gave a beautiful interview out there, man.
She went from, I think, personal trainer
to then launching a fitness app
that sold for 400 amps, guys.
Crazy good interview and game
for all the entrepreneurs watching right now.
We gotta go get this next one, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
I had a question for you.
How did you get?
Rich.
Real quick.
How did you guys get rich?
Oh, I'm not rich.
No.
How about him?
New York City rich?
I'm poor.
No, how about him right here?
He's also New York City poor.
We're both poor.
All right, guys.
Have a good one.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
I got a question for you.
How did you get rich?
I'm so broke, I can't pay attention.
I'm only kidding.
How did you get rich, man?
I go all over the world.
You're one of the richest people.
So you see the trucks?
I was in the logistics business.
I ran a big trucking company, sold it.
So you're a business owner?
I'm a business owner.
I started from nothing.
Two trucks, empty warehouse.
Built a lot of real estate.
How much did you sell your company for?
A lot of money.
Give me a range.
Over 500.
發胖就是這樣
You sold a company for $500 million.
I'd give you your four minute real quick.
Sure.
Is that okay?
How did you get the money to start your business?
Did you come from a lot of money?
No.
My father was just an average guy.
He had a small little business.
I took it over with $68 and built it up.
So you went from $68 to over?
It was a receivable of $68.
I took the $68 and I parlayed it.
And I bought all my
equipment and I built it up.
And from that, we were land pigs.
So I wound up with a lot of real estate.
And that's really what I do now.
So when I sold the business,
we converted more into real estate.
So let me ask you this, because
trucking, logistics, this isn't necessarily a super
sexy business that people don't think about.
But you can make a lot of money doing it.
How did you end up in this space?
I ended up in this space
because I loved what I did, right?
I loved the smell of diesel in the morning.
Every morning for me was like Christmas morning.
I like to get up, like to get out there.
A lot of kids don't want to do that today.
And that's a big problem.
They're looking at what other
people do and think it's easy.
But you got to fight.
And you got to get in there every single day.
And they don't.
It's what you got to do.
How old are you now?
I'm 60.
You got almost 40 years on me.
Whose generation works harder?
Yours or mine?
Oh, no.
You guys will forget about it.
You guys got, you're done.
I mean, I don't know what
you guys are going to do.
Truth be told, we are the last
of the generations that really could do it.
But how can somebody my age stand out?
It's like anything else.
You watch a baseball player, right?
What makes him better than the next guy?
It's how much you put into it.
And a lot of people don't
want to put the time in.
I can tell you from every morning getting up,
every night coming home late, I had to deal
with customers.
I had all the big Fortune 100 companies.
You name them, which I won't.
But every one that you could think of,
every retailer, I brought that freight to that store.
So that's what we did.
And then from that, like I said, we needed land.
And we bought a lot of land.
Now, today, we have over 1,000
tenants in all of our real estate.
So we're doing okay.
So what's the secret to creating wealth in real estate?
Because we know that most millionaires
and billionaires, they make their fortune.
Don't have debt.
I'm a debt-free operator, right?
So that's key.
Because if there's a mistake, you can rebound.
And a lot of guys leverage all the debt up.
And they want to talk
about how many buildings they own.
But they're so broke because they're leveraged up.
We have no leverage.
You don't like debt?
No, zero debt.
I ran my business with no debt.
So when I sold, it was a cash-free, debt-free deal.
All the money went in my pocket.
How did you get the capital to scale, though?
Because even companies like Apple, they borrow.
I never borrowed a dime to run my business.
I swear to you, in 40
years, I never borrowed a dime.
The only thing I borrowed money on was brand-new trucks.
So when I bought a brand-new
truck, I expensed it over one year.
And I paid it over four.
And that's what we did.
And we built it up.
And we kept the truck for 10 years.
So over time, we were able
to build a good cash network.
Take me back to the most
life-changing conversation that you've ever had.
What is the greatest piece of
advice you've ever received throughout your career?
I'm going to tell you.
So I'm from New York.
I'm Italian.
So a dear friend of my
father's takes me out to lunch.
And he tells me, kid, forget about all the bullshit.
Go to work every single day.
And I was young, and
I looked at all the bullshit.
And I thought, that's the right way to go.
But I got up, and I went to work.
And nothing stopped me.
I never left a soldier behind.
Failure is not an option.
It's all I can tell anybody who's looking
at your show or your channel, whatever it is,
because I don't know what you do.
But I'm telling you, you can't fail.
Just attack every day.
Are these your kids right here?
Yes, they are.
They both are.
Yeah.
And I have two more that are not here.
Let me ask you this.
A lot of people, when they have
families and they pass money down to generations,
they end up blowing the money.
What's a financial piece of wisdom right here
that you were going to instill in them
before you leave this earth?
Listen, there's no free rolls in my bakery.
They got to work for it.
They come to work.
My son here, he comes to work.
He's a beast.
He works every single day.
She's in college.
I'm very proud of what my kids have done.
They're really good kids.
But at the end of the day, we decided
to sell our business because we thought that the path
of real estate was going to be
a better one, which is great for them.
It's generational wealth.
Can I see the watch real quick?
Sure.
So you have a house on your wrist, right?
I sure do.
I have a few of them.
A few good cars, too.
But no, like I said, you
have to live large in every category.
And a lot of people don't.
A trait that I've noticed in really successful
people like yourself is that you're in incredible
shape.
Is there a correlation between
physical fitness and financial success?
Oh, 100%.
If you've got the discipline to go to the
gym every single day and take care of yourself,
it starts right here.
Do you believe in God?
Yeah, absolutely.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, the Holy Spirit, my buddy.
How did you know God was real?
When I sold my business two months
later, I had a massive heart attack.
You had a heart attack?
I had a heart attack.
Yes.
And my survival rate in
the hospital was 11%, outside 5%.
It was in the Widowmaker.
My son and his dog saved my life.
Got me to the hospital.
You want to wake up?
That's a wake-up call.
Wow.
And you knew that God
was with you in that moment?
Did you have people that doubted you?
Oh, are you kidding me?
Look at me.
I'm as dumb as a box of rocks.
I got a third-grade education.
I'm not a schooled guy.
You didn't listen to them, though?
No.
Why not?
Because I know I was better than that.
And I know what I wanted, and
I was going to go for it.
My last one for you.
If me and you died tomorrow, and you had
one more message to leave with the younger generation,
what would that be?
Be 10 minutes early to everything you do.
Think about tomorrow, because it's going to come.
I'm telling you it's going to come.
As much as you are 20
years old, you don't think about it.
If you run your life a little bit ahead
of where you are, so if today's Monday, you're
thinking about Thursday, and you're thinking
out, and five-year plans, that's what you
got to do, because a
lot of kids don't do that.
I know when I was a kid, that was one
of the things that I thought I always did right,
because I always looked forward.
From a paper route, I started a lawn route.
I started a tree removal business, sold all that.
And then, you know, my father had this small business.
Like I said, two trucks, an empty west.
That's not an exaggeration.
That's the truth.
You got amazing advice, sir.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for
your time, and I appreciate you.
Take care.
Lots of luck.
I connect with all the
millionaires and billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Yeah, absolutely.
Guys, we just interviewed another billionaire
out here in New York City.
But you know what I've realized
from interviewing hundreds of millionaires and billionaires
on this channel?
It's that most people don't fail because they lack ideas.
They fail because they never start.
They're allergic to execution.
Listen very carefully.
When I was first getting started, I had a
mentor tell me one time that the most valuable,
the most successful...
Spence a piece of real estate.
You know where it is?
It's in graveyards because there's billion-dollar ideas
sitting in the ground on people that
never took action.
I remember my own day one.
I had ideas.
I had ambition.
But I had a million excuses.
I didn't know the first step to start a business.
I didn't know how to build a website.
And honestly, that hesitancy almost stopped me.
But that's why I like Hostinger for every
entrepreneur because it makes it so easy to
get started, easier than it ever has been before.
Because Hostinger has an all-in-one platform.
Website.
Domain.
AI tools.
Automation.
Email marketing.
So you don't need...
You don't need to go to five different places.
Everything is in one place.
It's everything you need to get started.
You can literally go from a simple prompt
to a live website or store in just minutes.
And the pricing actually makes sense if you're starting out.
You don't need a huge budget
to look professional from day one.
You just need to get started.
So this new year, look, if you're ready to
turn that one day I'm going to do this into
day one and make this the best
year of your life, waste no more time.
Go down.
Click the link in the description of this video.
To get started with Hostinger today, we're also
going to put the link right here on the
screen.
For you to check out, use code SOHK for
10% off and take advantage of the new year's
sale while you still can.
With that being said, let's go get this next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
I had a question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I was 21.
21 years old.
And how did you get rich?
God made me a millionaire.
God made you a millionaire.
Who is your God?
Jesus Christ, my Lord and Savior.
And what's your name?
My name is Jameis Winston.
And what do you do?
And I'm the NFL quarterback
for the New York Football Giants.
And I go all over the world interviewing
the richest people to help the younger generation.
Could I get a minute with
you for the channel real quick?
Yeah, of course.
Is that cool?
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
Twenty, twenty-five million, actually.
Twenty-five million dollars?
What happened that year?
I got drafted.
What did you do with that money
when you first started to make it?
I mean, a lot of athletes go broke, right?
Yeah, I just let it sit.
I really worked off my endorsement money.
I didn't really touch my game money.
Did you come from a lot of money?
No, I didn't.
You didn't come from money.
So, you didn't come from a rich family, but
a rich family is going to come from you.
A wealthy family is going to come from me.
Three generations behind me.
Through the choices.
Through the choices and decisions that we make.
How long have you been in the NFL?
Eleven years.
A lot of people come into the league.
The average span is maybe two, three years.
It's not that long.
What was your secret to that longevity?
How were you in the league over ten years?
I feel like gratitude.
Gratitude is the key to abundance
and hard work and never giving up.
Never giving up.
Was there ever a time
where you wanted to give up?
There are always times where I want to give
up, but my dad, he told me the three rules
of life.
That's God.
That's education.
And you can do anything you put your mind to.
And the three rules of football was never
give up, never give up, never give up.
So, you had that belief, though.
That was the belief.
The third rule was believe in
anything that you put your mind to.
Yeah.
It started with the first.
It was God.
It was my faith.
My faith in God helped me to endure
and go through anything that I experienced along
the way.
So, even if I had some doubt or fear, even
if I were thinking too high of myself, I knew
that I could fall back on God and that
He would have me wherever I needed to be.
Hey, this is a Bible study
that the people need right now.
It's simple things, man.
It's bigger than you.
And I think when you understand that you have
a creator that put you here for a very unique
purpose, you understand that.
That purpose isn't going to get figured out overnight.
That purpose is developed.
It's groomed.
It's nurtured.
Somebody doesn't believe in God, what
would your message be to them?
My message would be to
you is find a local church.
You have a creator.
You have someone that loves you dearly.
Jesus Christ died on the cross for
us and He saved us for our sins.
These worldly things, they're here.
These trees and stuff, they're going
to be here for a good while.
But we are only here for a vapor.
So, how can you be an influence?
How can you impact someone
else to serve a high calling?
The calling.
The calling is the calling that you
were called to ultimately on this earth.
Can I tell you something?
What's up, Jay?
That was a beautiful interview, dude.
I appreciate it.
Thank you so much for your time.
Thank you, man.
That was awesome, man.
I connect with all the
millionaires and billionaires I interview.
Can I get your contact?
Yeah, absolutely.
You can get my contact.
Thanks, my friend.
Guys, we just walked up on
and interviewed the legend, Jameis Winston.
Made over $25 million in a single year
and he just gave a beautiful interview for everybody
watching right now, man.
He said, look, go to that
local church and go find God.
And I know that we interviewed lots
of millionaires and billionaires on this channel.
We talk a lot about money.
But let me tell you right now.
He just gave some of the
best life advice that I've ever heard.
Go find God and go make it happen, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
Oh, hey.
Nice to meet you.
Hey.
How did he get rich?
No.
You got to ask him.
He got the best story in America.
You're my hero, brother.
Sir.
How did you get rich?
Oh, you won't believe it.
No.
How did you get rich, man?
How did you get rich?
I shred junk metal cars for a living.
Shred junk cars?
Yeah.
It's that glamorous.
How long have you been a doctor for?
Do you work?
It's got to be like 35, 40 years.
Seriously?
And over these 40 years, what was the most
amount of money you made in a single year?
Probably like 60 or 70 million.
Shredding junk cars?
Yeah.
Could I interview you for a minute real quick?
I grew a channel to 20 million followers,
interviewing the richest people to help the younger generation.
Can I get one minute with
you real quick for our channel?
Yeah, sure.
Is that cool?
Yes, sir.
Do you think everybody's built for entrepreneurship?
I mean, it's tough.
It's not as glamorous as like my eyes are bloodshot.
You don't sleep much.
It's not that sexy.
What is the hardest part about being
a CEO of a company of your size?
Like how much is your company worth today?
It's got to be worth like a billion.
A billion dollars?
Yeah.
So as you were growing the business, it is very
common for people to run into those problems with ego.
How did you kind of come back to earth, like
have that humility, maintain at the front and center of everything?
I mean, when I got arrested, that
takes the ego out of your life.
You know, when you lose everything and you
have to rebuild it and you're in the paper.
And, you know, I think that strips away the ego
and you get a little more humble down the road.
But when I was younger,
I was like cocky and arrogant.
And I paid the price.
Are you a good negotiator?
One through ten, I'm a seven and a half.
You're a seven and a half?
Yeah, one through ten, I'm a seven and a half.
I've seen others.
I got friends that are way better negotiators than me.
But you're honest, man.
And I respect that.
A lot of people say, no, I'm the best.
No, I'm not the best.
I just work really hard.
What's your name?
Adam Weitzman.
How did you get the money to start your business?
Did you have a lot
of money when you started out?
No, loans.
I took bank loans.
I was really over leveraged in the beginning.
It was a total shit show.
Were you actually?
It was bad.
Did you end up paying off
all those loans though, I'm sure?
Yeah, you ended up paying them off.
But it was tough, you know.
But leverage is part of the growth.
But at this point in my life
that I'm older, the leverage days are over.
What is the lesson about money
that banks don't want people to know?
I just think you got to
watch the small print that you're signing.
That's why I say really small print.
Get a magnifying glass before you sign that stuff.
And definitely don't sign anything
without having somebody look over it.
What do you mean by the small print?
You know, like when you sign
a bank loan or credit card thing,
it gets really small at the bottom.
You might want to read that stuff.
You got to be careful.
You got to be careful because you're signing away.
When you guarantee something, you're liable.
I'm going to challenge you right now.
Take me back to the most
life-changing conversation you ever had
from all the people you've met,
the friends, the mentors you've had.
What is the greatest piece of advice that you received
that you would pass on to the younger generation?
When I was driving to prison and I asked
my dad if he had any advice for me,
and I thought he was going
to say this really long thing.
And he just looked at me
and said, don't be a p****.
So that was it.
Straight up.
And I'm sure that you
thought about that conversation many times.
And it really works because we all have like roadblocks.
We all have bad stuff happen.
But you can't just feel sorry for yourself.
You got to keep pushing through.
And that's how I've gotten to where I am today.
And that's how I'm going to continue.
And hopefully I have three daughters
and hopefully they have that inside too.
So you learned that nobody was coming to save you.
No, you have to save yourself.
No one's going to fix it.
There's no money tree in the backyard.
Nothing.
How long were you in prison for?
A year.
You were there for a year.
But it's not just a year in prison.
It's the time leading up to it because
you know you're in that flux when you're arrested.
The delta between arrested and going to prison.
It was like four years.
So that's just as bad as the prison.
What did you go to prison for?
It was called check hiding.
It's a transfer of funds.
Like making an invisible float.
I was guilty.
I'm sure you were at rock
bottom when you had first gotten out.
Yeah, it was really bad.
It was.
But what was that actionable step that you took?
Like let's talk to somebody.
They're at rock bottom right now.
They want to follow in your footsteps one day.
Build a multi-million dollar,
billion dollar company like you.
What's that first actionable step that they need
to take to get on the right track?
You just got to stay
focused and you got to sacrifice.
Did you sacrifice a lot?
A lot.
Like you know I try not to put
myself in positions that I have to make.
Like you know I think we know in life sometimes when we're
going to make a bad choice that it's a bad choice automatically.
But I try not to even put myself
in situations that I have to make that choice.
Is there any other tactical advice that you received
in the last couple of years from a mentor,
somebody in business that you
want to pass on to them?
I just think you never believe your own hype.
Don't believe your propaganda.
Don't.
You got to just always look in the
mirror and just like money is a mirage.
My biggest strength is I can be happy with nothing.
Really?
A hundred percent.
I don't need fancy cars.
I don't need jets.
I don't need to live at this place.
You know that's the best thing about prison.
You know like I can live without anything.
I've interviewed a lot of billionaires.
A lot of people say that they're miserable.
Are you happy?
Right now I'm happy as f**k.
Yeah.
Are you happy?
It's the happiest I've ever been in my life.
I've got great kids.
I've got three young daughters that are great.
Got a small good circle of friends.
What is it that keeps so many people
depressed and miserable especially when they become so successful?
I don't know because everybody is in a tough world.
It's tough but we're tougher.
You know we're made to exist and to survive.
So everybody has things.
We have problems and I'm not going to
speak for other people's problems but with mine,
our problems are so little
compared to other people's problems.
So I just appreciate what I
have every day and again you can't.
The money thing is great.
It's great to have nice things.
It's good to have nice clothes, watches, whatever.
But in the end of the day,
if that drives your happiness, it's not sustainable.
You've got amazing advice my friend.
I'm trying my friend.
Thank you so much man.
I appreciate you man.
I connect with all the billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Yeah, of course.
Is that cool?
Yeah sure, of course.
Hard Knocks family, that's a wrap on today's video.
I need you to stop
right now and do three things.
Like.
Subscribe.
And comment on who had
the best interview in today's video.
But let's go a step further.
I want to give you
direct access to my billionaire Network.
I'm not kidding.
Let me explain.
If you go down right now to the link in the description of this video, you can get direct access to live calls that I host every single week
with the eight-figure, nine-figure, and billionaire entrepreneurs that I interview on this channel where you ask them your questions directly and they mentor you live every week inside this community.
So I can't wait to see you
on the inside of the School of Mentors.
But.
With that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.